A Guide to the Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A19, McEachran House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A19, McEachran House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A19, McEachran House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A9, Floris School (White), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A9, Floris School (White), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A9, Floris School (White), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A2, Ohgren House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A2, Ohgren House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A2, Ohgren House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A2, Ohgren House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A3, Myers House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A3, Myers House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A6, Cherok House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A6, Cherok House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A6, Cherok House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A6, Cherok House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A6, Cherok House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Cherok House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Fox House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-14, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A5, Stover House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #:, Miscellaneous - Sign next to Wrenn House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #:, Miscellaneous - Sign next to Wrenn House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A6, Launders House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A9, White House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A9, White House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A9, White House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A9, White House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A9, White House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A10, Hatfield House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A10, Hatfield House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A10, Hatfield House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A10, Hatfield House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A10, Hatfield House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A3, Dairy Barns, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A3, Dairy Barns, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A3, Dairy Barns, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-15, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Fox House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Fox House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Fox House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Fox House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A7, Fox House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A8, Higgins House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A8, Higgins House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A8, Higgins House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A8, Higgins House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A8, Higgins House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House (site after demolition), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House (site after demolition), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A6, Launders House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A6, Launders House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A6, Launders House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-16, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A8, Bailey House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A10, Hatfield House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A9, Plotner House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A9, Plotner House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A9, Plotner House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A9, Plotner House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A9, Plotner House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A9, Plotner House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A7, Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: no site, Barn at 2800 Centreville Road, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-17, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A11, Haygood House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A11, Haygood House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A11, Haygood House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A11, Haygood House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A11, Haygood House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A11, Haygood House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-18, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A9, Chantilly Cash & Carry, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A9, Chantilly Cash & Carry, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A9, Chantilly Cash & Carry, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A9, Chantilly Cash & Carry, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A9, Chantilly Cash & Carry, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A8, Kwik Chef Texas BBQ, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: no site, Unknown, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-19, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-20, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 25-4-A1, Walled Cemetery, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-4-A1, Walled Cemetery, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Mitchell Weeks House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A3, Dodd House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-21, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A6, Corncrib, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A6, Corncrib, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A6, Corncrib, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A6, Corncrib, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A7, Oakton Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A5, Store, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A8, Kwik Chef Texas BBQ, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A8, Kwik Chef Texas BBQ, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-22, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-23, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A12, Kerlin House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-24, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 36-3-A1, Appledore, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A6, Log House Ruin, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A6, Log House Ruin, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A6, Log House Ruin, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A6, Log House Ruin, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A6, Log House Ruin, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A6, Log House Ruin, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A7, Log House Ruin #2, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A7, Log House Ruin #2, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A7, Log House Ruin #2, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A7, Log House Ruin #2, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A5, Outbuilding and Stone Foundation, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-25, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A2, House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A2, House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A2, House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A2, House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A3, Outbuilding, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A3, Outbuilding, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A12, Testa House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-26, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A5, Langham House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A8, Dairy Farm (Evans), 1985 May; Roll #: 85-27, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A2, Caldwell House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A3, Presgraves House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-28, Frame #: 008